<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Friendly Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="soc">The University\'s School of Computing was founded in 2018. It was created
    to cater to the needs of departments that were more related to computer science than general science.
    It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="saat">The School of Agriculture and Agricultural Technology is foremost among the
    six schools of FUTA established in 1982. It has programs in agricultural and natural resources
    management. It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA. </string>
    <string name="seet">The School of Engineering and Engineering Technology was established in 1988,
    seven years after the Federal University of Technology, Akure came into exixtence. It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="sos">The School of Science is one of the schools established at the inception of the
    university in 1982. Presently, the School of Sciences consists of nine departments namely; Biochemistry,
    Biology, Chemistry, Mathematical Sciences, General Studies, Microbiology, Physics, Statistics and Biotechnology.
    It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="sems">The School of Earth and Mineral Sciences is one of the Schools in FUTA aimed at
    making a strong positive impact on the nation\'s positive impact on the nation\'s mineral industry
    and on the application of climate information for sustainable development. It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="set">The School of Environmental Technology is a school in FUTA with a mission
    to promote inter-disciplinary research, service-based learning and innovative course content delivery
    towards solving environmental problems through the application of technology and promotion of sustainable
    built-environment. It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="lib">The University Library, FUTA was established in 1982 with the an aim to build
    up intellectual resources in all formats that will support technological drive of the university
    by providing conducive environment for research, teaching and learning that will encourage development
    of products that are technologically oriented and self-reliant. The library is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="crc">The Computer Resource Centre FUTA serves as the Information and Communication
    Technology nerve center of the university. It is located beside the School of Computing in the
    Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="health">FUTA Health Centre is located along obakere road, FUTA South Gate.</string>
    <string name="capacity">The FUTA 2500 Capcity Auditorium is the biggest auditorium on campus.
    It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="senate">The Senate Building in FUTA is responsible for the coordination of all academic
    activities in the university. It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
    <string name="affairs">The Student Affairs is a division of dedicated people committed
    to support students in their studies, social growth, and well-being in reaching their highest
    potentials while at the University. It is located in the Obanla campus of FUTA.</string>
</resources>
